
// Notes for the color arrangement:
// Red: 2021 -> Now 
// Blue: 2016 -> 2020 
// Yellow: 2012 -> 2015

const Questions = [
    {
        question: "Life goes around and round<br/>I've stumbled and stopped moving on",
        answer: "A Turtle's Heart",
        album: "Mag Mell",
        color: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "Ever since I was young<br/>I had a dream that I will be living in a castle<br/>Made out of chocolate and cake<br/>What a sweet sweet dream it was",
        answer: "Chocological",
        album: "Mag Mell",
        color: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "Tick-tock<br/>Time doesn't stop<br/>Prepare your doubts<br/>Eat them up",
        answer: "Utosphere",
        album: "Mag Mell",
        color: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "Find a future<br/>Find a land of dreams<br/>Find a heaven<br/>Find a home that won't leave you<br/>No matter how long you've been lost",
        answer: "Rosetta",
        album: "Mag Mell",
        color: "yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "I'll be a robot that throws all your tears into the trashcan",
        answer: "Rubber Human",
        album: "Millennium Mother",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Each one of us is a bucket of love<br/>Some of us empty, some of us filled up",
        answer: "world.search(you);",
        album: "Millennium Mother",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "For the first time you failed and I asked myself<br/>Is there meaning at all?",
        answer: "Extension of You",
        album: "Millennium Mother",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Now that you're gone so much lemonade gets left over<br/>Waiting to be drank<br/>I wish that person could be you",
        answer: "Lemonade",
        album: "Millennium Mother",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "That's when I've realized<br/>We've became family",
        answer: "RTRT",
        album: "Miracle Milk",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "There's no undo and there's no repeat<br/>Can't go back to how we used to be<br/>There's no restart but only proceed<br/>Take up from where we've left off and see",
        answer: "Ga1ahad and Scientific Witchery",
        album: "Miracle Milk",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Why are we always separated by bulletproof walls<br/>Then I learned that this emptiness could be love<br/>That it could be love, it must be love",
        answer: "Sl0t",
        album: "Miracle Milk",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Bad chromosomes or sad broken toes<br/>Cure it up with my heavenly milk",
        answer: "Painful Death for the Lactose Intolerant",
        album: "Miracle Milk",
        color: "blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Children of th–µ city sees only the neon stars<br/>Reflected upon the murky gutter sky<br/>Don't ask me why<br/>I desperately wish to be included in the city's night",
        answer: "Children of the city",
        album: "To Kill a Living Book -for Library Of Ruina-",
        color: "red"
    },
    {
        question: "It pains me to think<br/>That my happiness turned out to be one of those fingers<br/>That strangled you until you couldn't breathe",
        answer: "Children of the city",
        album: "To Kill a Living Book -for Library Of Ruina-",
        color: "red"
    },
    {
        question: "With tears rolling down our faces<br/>We began to sing<br/>'They can never take anything from our souls'<br/>Louder and louder",
        answer: "Children of the city",
        album: "To Kill a Living Book -for Library Of Ruina-",
        color: "red"
    },
    {
        question: "Cut it off, you've already lost<br/>All that precious bravery is gonna get you hurt<br/>In a world that feeds on the minority",
        answer: "Children of the city",
        album: "To Kill a Living Book -for Library Of Ruina-",
        color: "red"
    },
]

export default Questions